http://www.holmesstamp.com/privacy-policy

Log OutMy Account Blog Customer ServiceLog In COMPANY STORE
Holmes Custom
Search
Shopping cart 0 items -
$0.00You have no items in your shopping cart.
Shop our products Holmes Custom Embossers & SealsDesk & Pocket Embossers & SealsAddress SealsCorporate Seal EmbossersCustom EmbossersNotary & Professional SealsNotary SealsArchitect SealsEngineer SealsLand Surveyor Seal EmbossersLandscape Architect SealsOther Professional SealsFace MasksDesign Your Own Non-Medical Cloth MasksAdult MasksChild MasksPromotional ProductsPromotional Products with Your LogoPlaques and AwardsDesign Your Own AwardsStanding AwardsAcrylic Glass Crystal AwardsArt Glass AwardsDesk ClocksPlaquesSmall PlaquesMedium PlaquesLarge PlaquesMultiple Plate PlaquesTrophiesSmall TrophiesMedium TrophiesLarge TrophiesEmployee AwardsAwards for EmployeesMonthlyQuarterlyYearlyOtherDonor AwardsHonoraryRecognitionGiftsGoal AwardsSalesDonationQuality ControlSafetyScholastic AwardsTeacherStudentAdminImprovedService & Career RecognitionService Recognition AwardsYearsRetirementIdentificationName TagsCustom Badges & Name TagsEngraved BadgesFull Color BadgesMagnetic Name TagsLogo Name TagsName Tag TemplatesRestaurantMedicalSalonReusable BadgesWooden Name TagsBadge FastenersLeatherette Name TagsVisitor BadgesFancy Name TagsPocket BadgesName PlatesWall Name PlatesDesk Name PlatesInsert OnlyPhoto IDsQuick Custom Photo IDsProducts for New EmployeesLuggage TagsCustom & Engraved Luggage TagsEngraved Key ChainsButtonsPortfoliosCustom Leatherette PortfoliosRubber Stamps & InksCustom Rubber StampsBrands & ModelsShop Stamps by Brand & ModelMaxLight by TrodatTrodat StampsTrodat Professional StampsTrodat Printy StampsTrodat DatersTrodat Ultifast StampsTrodat Replacement Pads and Ink BottlesIdeal by Trodat2000 Plus ModelsInks & Replacement PadsWood Hand StampsEuropean Hand StampsTraditional Hand StampsUp to 1" Wide Up to 2" WideUp to 3" WideUp to 4" WideUp to 5" WideUp to 6" WideUp to 7" WideOffice StampsInspection StampsSignature StampsSignature/Initial OnlyWith DateWith Printed NameCustom Line StampsBusiness & Office StampsBanking & Accounting StampsDeposit StampsStock Office StampsQR Code StampsProfessional StampsNotary StampsArchitect StampsEngineer StampsSurveyor StampsDesigner StampsDaterCustom Daters StampsAll Dater StampsTrodat Professional Logo StampsRubber Custom Logo StampsInked StampsWood Handle StampsLogo & Text StampsCatalog StampsAddress StampsPersonalized Return Address StampsWedding StampsCouples Stamps & Wedding StampsTeacher StampsCustom Teacher StampsInks & Stamps PadsInk Pad Replacements & Refill Ink BottlesSign ShopOffice & Workplace SignsCreate Your OwnAluminumPlasticClear AcrylicBrass Signs & PlatesBusiness & FacilityParkingStore HoursNavigation & Direction Projection SignsTabletop SignsOpen for Business SignsStick OnAdhesive & Magnetic SignageFloor DecalsStencilsMagnetic SignsDecalsSafety SignsOSHAWarningCautionDangerEmergency Eye Wash StationFire EmergencyNotice SignsPool SafetyRequired SignsWash HandsADA SignageSmoking & VapingStairs & ElevatorsMax CapacityRestroomsVinyl BannersAuto SignsCar MagnetsLicense PlatesBumper StickersProperty SignsBeware of Dog SignsNo Dumping SignsNo Guns SignsNo Trespassing SignsRecycling SignsYard SignsAddress SignsSocial Distancing SignsNo Soliciting SignsTake Out, To-Go and Curbside Pickup SignsOffice & School SignsSign AccessoriesSign Holders & AccessoriesReal Estate GiftsReal Estate Gifts DrinkwareCustom DrinkwareCutting BoardsCustom Cutting Board GiftsKey ChainsReal Estate Keychain GiftYard & Garden FlagsPersonalized Garden Flag GiftsCorporate Gift GuideAll CategoriesCloseHomeEmbossers & SealsDesk & Pocket Embossers & SealsAddress SealsCorporate Seal EmbossersCustom EmbossersNotary & Professional SealsNotary SealsArchitect SealsEngineer SealsLand Surveyor Seal EmbossersLandscape Architect SealsOther Professional SealsFace MasksDesign Your Own Non-Medical Cloth MasksAdult MasksChild MasksPromotional ProductsPromotional Products with Your LogoPlaques and AwardsDesign Your Own AwardsStanding AwardsAcrylic Glass Crystal AwardsArt Glass AwardsDesk ClocksPlaquesSmall PlaquesMedium PlaquesLarge PlaquesMultiple Plate PlaquesTrophiesSmall TrophiesMedium TrophiesLarge TrophiesEmployee AwardsAwards for EmployeesMonthlyQuarterlyYearlyOtherDonor AwardsHonoraryRecognitionGiftsGoal AwardsSalesDonationQuality ControlSafetyScholastic AwardsTeacherStudentAdminImprovedService & Career RecognitionService Recognition AwardsYearsRetirementIdentificationName TagsCustom Badges & Name TagsEngraved BadgesFull Color BadgesMagnetic Name TagsLogo Name TagsName Tag TemplatesRestaurantMedicalSalonReusable BadgesWooden Name TagsBadge FastenersLeatherette Name TagsVisitor BadgesFancy Name TagsPocket BadgesName PlatesWall Name PlatesDesk Name PlatesInsert OnlyPhoto IDsQuick Custom Photo IDsProducts for New EmployeesLuggage TagsCustom & Engraved Luggage TagsEngraved Key ChainsButtonsPortfoliosCustom Leatherette PortfoliosRubber Stamps & InksCustom Rubber StampsBrands & ModelsShop Stamps by Brand & ModelMaxLight by TrodatTrodat StampsTrodat Professional StampsTrodat Printy StampsTrodat DatersTrodat Ultifast StampsTrodat Replacement Pads and Ink BottlesIdeal by Trodat2000 Plus ModelsInks & Replacement PadsWood Hand StampsEuropean Hand StampsTraditional Hand StampsUp to 1" Wide Up to 2" WideUp to 3" WideUp to 4" WideUp to 5" WideUp to 6" WideUp to 7" WideOffice StampsInspection StampsSignature StampsSignature/Initial OnlyWith DateWith Printed NameCustom Line StampsBusiness & Office StampsBanking & Accounting StampsDeposit StampsStock Office StampsQR Code StampsProfessional StampsNotary StampsArchitect StampsEngineer StampsSurveyor StampsDesigner StampsDaterCustom Daters StampsAll Dater StampsTrodat Professional Logo StampsRubber Custom Logo StampsInked StampsWood Handle StampsLogo & Text StampsCatalog StampsAddress StampsPersonalized Return Address StampsWedding StampsCouples Stamps & Wedding StampsTeacher StampsCustom Teacher StampsInks & Stamps PadsInk Pad Replacements & Refill Ink BottlesSign ShopOffice & Workplace SignsCreate Your OwnAluminumPlasticClear AcrylicBrass Signs & PlatesBusiness & FacilityParkingStore HoursNavigation & Direction Projection SignsTabletop SignsOpen for Business SignsStick OnAdhesive & Magnetic SignageFloor DecalsStencilsMagnetic SignsDecalsSafety SignsOSHAWarningCautionDangerEmergency Eye Wash StationFire EmergencyNotice SignsPool SafetyRequired SignsWash HandsADA SignageSmoking & VapingStairs & ElevatorsMax CapacityRestroomsVinyl BannersAuto SignsCar MagnetsLicense PlatesBumper StickersProperty SignsBeware of Dog SignsNo Dumping SignsNo Guns SignsNo Trespassing SignsRecycling SignsYard SignsAddress SignsSocial Distancing SignsNo Soliciting SignsTake Out, To-Go and Curbside Pickup SignsOffice & School SignsSign AccessoriesSign Holders & AccessoriesReal Estate GiftsReal Estate Gifts DrinkwareCustom DrinkwareCutting BoardsCustom Cutting Board GiftsKey ChainsReal Estate Keychain GiftYard & Garden FlagsPersonalized Garden Flag GiftsCorporate Gift GuideBlogAbout UsMeet the teamCareersContact UsPressCategoriesEmbossers & SealsDesk & Pocket Embossers & SealsAddress SealsCorporate Seal EmbossersCustom EmbossersNotary & Professional SealsNotary SealsArchitect SealsEngineer SealsLand Surveyor Seal EmbossersLandscape Architect SealsOther Professional SealsFace MasksDesign Your Own Non-Medical Cloth MasksAdult MasksChild MasksPromotional ProductsPromotional Products with Your LogoPlaques and AwardsDesign Your Own AwardsStanding AwardsAcrylic Glass Crystal AwardsArt Glass AwardsDesk ClocksPlaquesSmall PlaquesMedium PlaquesLarge PlaquesMultiple Plate PlaquesTrophiesSmall TrophiesMedium TrophiesLarge TrophiesEmployee AwardsAwards for EmployeesMonthlyQuarterlyYearlyOtherDonor AwardsHonoraryRecognitionGiftsGoal AwardsSalesDonationQuality ControlSafetyScholastic AwardsTeacherStudentAdminImprovedService & Career RecognitionService Recognition AwardsYearsRetirementIdentificationName TagsCustom Badges & Name TagsEngraved BadgesFull Color BadgesMagnetic Name TagsLogo Name TagsName Tag TemplatesRestaurantMedicalSalonReusable BadgesWooden Name TagsBadge FastenersLeatherette Name TagsVisitor BadgesFancy Name TagsPocket BadgesName PlatesWall Name PlatesDesk Name PlatesInsert OnlyPhoto IDsQuick Custom Photo IDsProducts for New EmployeesLuggage TagsCustom & Engraved Luggage TagsEngraved Key ChainsButtonsPortfoliosCustom Leatherette PortfoliosRubber Stamps & InksCustom Rubber StampsBrands & ModelsShop Stamps by Brand & ModelMaxLight by TrodatTrodat StampsTrodat Professional StampsTrodat Printy StampsTrodat DatersTrodat Ultifast StampsTrodat Replacement Pads and Ink BottlesIdeal by Trodat2000 Plus ModelsInks & Replacement PadsWood Hand StampsEuropean Hand StampsTraditional Hand StampsUp to 1" Wide Up to 2" WideUp to 3" WideUp to 4" WideUp to 5" WideUp to 6" WideUp to 7" WideOffice StampsInspection StampsSignature StampsSignature/Initial OnlyWith DateWith Printed NameCustom Line StampsBusiness & Office StampsBanking & Accounting StampsDeposit StampsStock Office StampsQR Code StampsProfessional StampsNotary StampsArchitect StampsEngineer StampsSurveyor StampsDesigner StampsDaterCustom Daters StampsAll Dater StampsTrodat Professional Logo StampsRubber Custom Logo StampsInked StampsWood Handle StampsLogo & Text StampsCatalog StampsAddress StampsPersonalized Return Address StampsWedding StampsCouples Stamps & Wedding StampsTeacher StampsCustom Teacher StampsInks & Stamps PadsInk Pad Replacements & Refill Ink BottlesSign ShopOffice & Workplace SignsCreate Your OwnAluminumPlasticClear AcrylicBrass Signs & PlatesBusiness & FacilityParkingStore HoursNavigation & Direction Projection SignsTabletop SignsOpen for Business SignsStick OnAdhesive & Magnetic SignageFloor DecalsStencilsMagnetic SignsDecalsSafety SignsOSHAWarningCautionDangerEmergency Eye Wash StationFire EmergencyNotice SignsPool SafetyRequired SignsWash HandsADA SignageSmoking & VapingStairs & ElevatorsMax CapacityRestroomsVinyl BannersAuto SignsCar MagnetsLicense PlatesBumper StickersProperty SignsBeware of Dog SignsNo Dumping SignsNo Guns SignsNo Trespassing SignsRecycling SignsYard SignsAddress SignsSocial Distancing SignsNo Soliciting SignsTake Out, To-Go and Curbside Pickup SignsOffice & School SignsSign AccessoriesSign Holders & AccessoriesReal Estate GiftsReal Estate Gifts DrinkwareCustom DrinkwareCutting BoardsCustom Cutting Board GiftsKey ChainsReal Estate Keychain GiftYard & Garden FlagsPersonalized Garden Flag GiftsCorporate Gift Guide
This privacy policy sets out how HCBrands.com (and its affiliates, as defined below) uses and protects any information that you give HCBrands.com when you use this website. HCBrands.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. HCBrands.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.Your Personal InformationWe do not collect personal information when you visit our web site unless you complete a contact form or are an existing customer.Our contact forms request your name (and/or business name), phone number, and e-mail address. This data is collected so that we may respond to your inquiries.We will not disclose your personal information to any person or business who is not an employee or agent of HCBrands.com. We may use your personal information to contact you as needed for business purposes, including but not limited to, soliciting feedback about our website, products, and services. We may also contact you to provide customer support, announce new services, or with requests for general information. We honor all requests for removal from any of our e-mail lists.We may share broad demographic or other information about our members with partner companies while withholding your personal identification.We do not share, sell, rent or barter any identifiable personal information to any third party without your permission. How We May Use Your Information:With your consent (where required by applicable law), we may use the information we collect for the following purposes:To send you emails or text messages about the products and services, competitions, offers, promotions or special events we believe may interest you;To send you emails or text messages about the products and services of our business partners;Use cookies and similar technologies;We may use the information we collect about you in other ways, which we will tell you about at the time we collect it and for which we will seek your consent if required by law. Marketing CommunicationsIf you have agreed to receive marketing communications from us, you can later opt out by following the opt-out instructions in the marketing communications we send you or you can also contact us by using the contact details provided under the “How to Contact Us” section above. You can opt out of email, SMS text message marketing, and push notification marketing at any time.If you do opt out of receiving marketing communications from us, we may still send communications to you about your transactions, as well as any accounts you have with us.
Opting out of one form of communication does not mean you’ve opted out of other forms as well.
For example, if you opt out of receiving marketing emails, you may still receive marketing text messages if you’ve opted in to receiving them. Additionally, opting out of one of our websites does not automatically opt you out of all of our websites marketing communications you have previously opted into.Demographic InformationWe may use user information, including Personal Information, behavioral metrics, geo-location data, demographic data and marketing preferences to personalize and display advertisements and other content for you.Newsletters and Product Notification Opt In/OutWe periodically send newsletters and/or new product updates and notifications. Visitors to our website may choose to receive these e-mails. Customers receiving e-mails can opt out in order to prevent receiving future e-mails of this nature. This option is provided at the bottom of every e-mail. We respect your right to decline and have made the process of opting out as easy as possible. Opting out of the newsletters does not remove you from our contact database and you may still receive invoices or emergency website notifications via e-mail.How We Use cookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Limitations of this Privacy PolicyHCBrands.com takes all reasonable care to protect your information; however, there can be exceptions to this policy whereby we are required to release information about you. Some possible reasons for exception to this policy include but are not limited to, government and court order requests. In the event such a situation arises, you authorize HCBrands.com to disclose any content or information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as HCBrands.com deems necessary or appropriate.Outside Source Content and MaterialHCBrands.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites which we may provide links to.Collection ConsentBy using our website, you consent to HCBrands.com collecting and using this information.List of Cookes We May CollectThe table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.COOKIE nameCOOKIE DescriptionCARTThe association with your shopping cart.CATEGORY_INFOStores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.COMPAREThe items that you have in the Compare Products list.CURRENCYYour preferred currencyCUSTOMERAn encrypted version of your customer id with the store.CUSTOMER_AUTHAn indicator if you are currently logged into the store.CUSTOMER_INFOAn encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDSStores the Customer Segment IDEXTERNAL_NO_CACHEA flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.FRONTENDYou sesssion ID on the server.GUEST-VIEWAllows guests to edit their orders.LAST_CATEGORYThe last category you visited.LAST_PRODUCTThe most recent product you have viewed.NEWMESSAGEIndicates whether a new message has been received.NO_CACHEIndicates whether it is allowed to use cache.PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CARTA link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.POLLThe ID of any polls you have recently voted in.POLLNInformation on what polls you have voted on.RECENTLYCOMPAREDThe items that you have recently compared.STFInformation on products you have emailed to friends.STOREThe store view or language you have selected.USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIEIndicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDSThe products that you have recently viewed.WISHLISTAn encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.WISHLIST_CNTThe number of items in your Wishlist. Changes To This PolicyAny future privacy policy changes will be posted on this page to keep you aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Affiliateswww.customstamps.com,www.simplystamps.com, www.nametagwizard.com, www.customsigns.com, www.promo180.com, www.904custom.com, www.corpconnect.com, www.allstatenotarysupplies.com, www.wallmonkeys.com
Company
facebook About UsCustomer ServiceContact UsBlog American MadeMy Account
facebook Login / Create AccountForgot PasswordManage AccountSupport
facebook ShippingReturnsReordersCoupon Questionsfacebookpinteresttwitterinstagramyou-tubeSave 10% off your order today, Sign up for Email
By signing up, you agree to our Terms and Conditions & Privacy Policy Business Products:Sign ShopRubber StampsNotary Seals & EmbossersName TagsName PlatesHC Brands:Made in AmericaTerms & ConditionsPrivacyCustomer ServiceReturnsCareers © 2020 HC Brands. All Rights Reserved.Guest ID: n31j2m Back to Top Login into your Account ×
Login Register
Forgot Your Password?
Forgot Your Password? ×Please enter your email address below. You will receive a link to reset your password.
Submit
Back to Login
Create an account × * All fields below are required.
Sign Up for NewsletterBy signing up, you agree to our Terms and Conditions & Privacy Policy
What's this? CloseChecking "Remember Me" will let you access your shopping cart on this computer when you are logged out Close
Submit
Back to Login
